A Guide to the Lyman Creighton Craig papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA134
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Manuscript materials, 1948-1976; 5
  - L.C. Craig "Countercurrent distribution", 1962 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    In: Florkin, M. and Stotz, E.H., eds., Comprehensive biochemistry. New York, Elsevier Publishing Co. v. 4, pp. 1-31.
    Galley proof with corrections only [Reprint of this ms not with collected papers].
  - L.C. Craig "Differential dialysis", 1964 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    Science 144, 1093-1099.
    Correspondence.
  - L.C. Craig, J.D. Fisher and T.P. King "Dialysis studies. IX. On the conformation stability of glucagon adrenocorticotropic hormone, and similar peptides", 1965 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    Biochemistry 4, 311-318.
    Correspondence; referee II comments on ms; corrected galley proof and typescript of ms; figures and working material.
  - M.A. Ruttenberg, T.P. King and L.C. Craig "The use of the tyrocidines for the study of conformational and aggregation behavior", 1965 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    JACS 87, 4196-4198.
    Typescript of ms and figure.
  - N. Hilschmann and L.C. Craig "Amino acid sequence studies with Bence-Jones proteins", 1965 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    PNAS 53, 1403-1409.
    Correspondence; photocopy of ms with corrections; figures; working material.
  - N. Hilschmann and L.C. Craig "Amino acid sequence studies with Bence-Jones proteins", 1965 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    Literature search (collection of reprints by others and by Craig and Hilschmann). Also includes handwritten note by Gerald M. Edelman with Edelman et al reprints.
  - L.C. Craig and E.J. Harfenist "The characterization of peptides by diffusion through membranes", 1965 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    In: European Peptide Symposium 6th, Athens, 1963. Peptides; proceedings. Oxford, Pergamon Press, pp. 373-382.
    Copy of ms [See also under: Theodoropoulos, D.M. in box no. 14].
  - L.C. Craig "Differential dialysis", 1965 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    In: Reilly, C.N. ed., Advances in analytical chemistry and instrumentation. New York, Interscience Publishers, v. 4, pp. 35-74.
    Printer's copy with corrections; figures.
  - G. Roncari, Z. Kurylo-Borowska, and L.C. Craig "On the chemical nature of the antibiotic edeine", 1966 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    Biochemistry 5, 2153-2159.
    Photocopy of ms; figures; working material.
  - L.C. Craig and T.P. King "Countercurrent distribution", 1966 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    In: Encyclopedia of industrial chemical analysis. New York, Interscience Publishers. v. 1, pp. 506-534.
    Correspondence; corrected galley proof and printer's photocopy of ms with corrections; also typescript of ms.
  - H. Meinardi and L.C. Craig "Studies of substance P", 1966 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    In: Erdos, E.G. and others, eds., Hypotensive peptides; proceedings of the International symposium, Oct. 25-29, 1965, Florence, Italy. New York, Springer, pp. 594-607.
    Typescript of ms; copies of original ms (?); working material and prints of figures [See also under: Meinardi, H. in box no. 8 for additional information on Int'l symp on hypotensive polypeptides].
  - R.C. Williams and L.C. Craig "A method of calculating countercurrent distribution curves of nonideal solutes", 1967 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    Separation science 2, 487-499.
    Correspondence; photocopy of ms.
  - L.C. Craig "The importance of selective separation methods in biochemistry", 1967 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    Cienca e investigacion, Buenos Aires 23, 116-? Photocopy of what appears to be presentation with slightly different title and figures.
    [Presented at 1966 Nov VII Panamerican congress of pharmacy and biochemistry in Buenos Aires].
  - L.C. Craig "Techniques for the study of peptides and proteins by dialysis and diffusion", 1967 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    In: Hirs, C.H.W., ed., Methods in enzymology. New York, Academic Press, v. XI, pp. 870-905.
  - L.C. Craig "The use of antibiotic peptides as models for the study of inter-and intramolecular forces in proteins", 1967 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    Ciencia e investigacin, Buenos Aires 23, 160-169.
    Photocopy of ms in English and published paper in Spanish; figures and working material [Presented at 1966 Nov Buenos Aires VII Panamerican congress of pharmacy and biochemistry].
  - P.T. Englund, T.P. King, L.C. Craig and Walti, A. "Studies on ficin I. Its isolation and characterization", 1968 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    Biochemistry 7, 1963-175.
    Correspondence; referee's comments; print of figure 10; working material; and photocopy of Englund, King and Craig ms "Studies on ficin II. Some chemical modifications" with referee's comments. (1967 Oct 3 Neurath to King correspondence indicates ms not published).
  - L.C. Craig "Dialysis and ultrafiltration", 1968 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    In: Williams, CA. and Chase, M.W., eds., Methods in immunology and immunochemistry.
    New York, Academic Press, v. 2, pp. 119-133. Correspondence; galley proofs (1 with corrections).
  - L.C. Craig, H.C Chen, M. Printz and Taylor, W.I. "Membrane separations", 1968 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    In: Characterization and macromolecular structure; Proceedings of a conference April 5, 1967. National Academy of Sciences, Washington, D.C. (1968) pp. 315-329. (National Research Council publication, 1573).
    Photocopy of ms and printed folder of conference report and table of contents of publication.
  - [NPI] Authors (not indicated) "Membrane separations" (Box 28, Folder 2)
    Photocopy of ms with prints of figures. (May never have been used).
    [#222 in bibliography same title].
  - L.C. Craig "Conformation studies with polypeptides by rotatory dispersion and thin film dialysis", 1968 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    PNAS 61, 152-159.
    Correspondence; photocopies of ms; some corrected and working material.
  - T.P. Hettinger and L.C. Craig "Edeine II. The composition of the antibiotic peptide edeine A", 1968 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    Biochemistry 7, 4147-4153.
    Galley proof with corrections.
  - L.C. Craig, H.C. Chen and W.I. Taylor "Thin film dialysis including counter-current dialysis", 1969 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    Journal of macromolecular science A: chemistry, A3, 133-149.
    Correspondence includes arrangements for presentation; program; photocopy of ms; working material [Presented at 1967 Oct 30 Anaheim, Calif. Symposium on synthetic and natural polymer membranes in medicine at the Pacific conference on chemistry and spectroscopy sponsored by ACS/Society of applied spectroscopy].
  - S.L. Laiken, M. Printz and L.C. Craig "Tritium-hydrogen exchange studies of protein models. I. Gramicidin S-A", 1969 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    Biochemistry 8, 519-526.
    Correspondence; photocopy of ms; referees comments on ms; corrected galley proof and working material.
  - [NPI] E. Gross, J.L. Morell and L.C. Craig "The presence of dehydroalanine in subtilin" (Box 28, Folder 7)
    [Submitted to JACS for publication but not accepted].
    Correspondence; copies of ms, one corrected copy; referee's comments; photocopies of Gross and Morell mss with referee comments. [See folder no. 8 in box no. 28].
  - E. Gross, J.L. Morell and L.C. Craig "Dehydroalanyllysine: identical COOH-terminal structure in the peptide antibiotics nisin and subtilin", 1969 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    PNAS 62 (1969) 952-956.
    Correspondence; various copies of ms; corrected galley proof and working material. [See also folder no. 7 in box no. 28].
  - L.C. Craig and H-C Chen "On rapid laboratory dialysis", 1969 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    Analytical chemistry 41, 590-596.
    Correspondence; photocopy of ms with figures.
  - L.C. Craig, W.F. Phillips and M. Burachik "Bacitracin A. Isolation by counter double current distribution and characterization", 1969 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    Biochemistry 8, 2348-2356.
    Correspondence; galley proof with corrections; photocopy of ms; photographs of figures and formula and working material.
  - A. Stern, W.A. Gibbons and L.C. Craig "Effect of association on the nuclear magnetic resonance spectra of tyrocidine B", 1969 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    JACS 91, 2794-2796.
    Correspondence; referee's comments on ms; photocopy of corrected ms; working material.
  - S. Laiken, M. Printz and L.C. Craig "Circular dichroism of the tyrocidines and gramicidin S-A", 1969 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    J biol chem 244, 4454-4457.
    Correspondence; referee's comments on ms; corrected galley proof; photocopy of ms and working material.
  - L.C. Craig, H-C Chen and E.J. Harfenist "Separations based on size and conformation", 1969 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    In: Gerritsen, Theo., ed., Modern separation methods of macromolecules and particles. New York, Wiley-Interscience. pp. 219-239. (Progress in separation and purification, 2) Presented at 1968 Feb 7-8 Madison, Wisc. University of Wisconsin symposium on modern separation methods of macromolecules and particles.
    Correspondence; photocopy and abstract of presentation; corrected galley proof; abstracts of presentations of participants; symposium programs and list of participants; list of faculty and graduate students participating in symp; general information and guide to University of Wisc campus; photocopy of Hoffman and Bock published paper.
    [Reprint of this ms not with collected papers].
    In: Li, Norman H., Matulevicius, E.S., Fels, M., eds., Recent advances in separation techniques. New York, American Institute of Chemical Engineers, pp. 1-6 (AIChE Symposium series, 120).
    Presented at 1971 Aug 29-Sept 1 Atlantic City, N.J. AIChE 70 Nat'l meeting.
    Correspondence; programs AEChE 68 and 70 Nat'l meetings and printed booklet of 70th annual meeting; photocopy of presentation with working material; photocopied published ms.
  - M. Burachik, L.C. Craig and J. Chang "Studies of self-association and conformation of peptides by thin-film dialysis", 1970 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    Biochemistry 9, 3293-3300.
  - K.K. Stewart, L.C. Craig and R.C. Williams "Computer calculation of escape curves of non-ideal solutes in thin film dialysis", 1970 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    Analytical chemistry 42, 1252-1257.
  - K.K. Stewart and L.C. Craig "Thin film dialysis studies with highly acetylated cellophane membranes", 1970 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    Analytical chemistry 42, 1257-1260.
    1 item correspondence.
  - T.P. Hettinger and L.C. Craig "Edeine. IV. Structure of the antibiotic peptides edeines A1 and B1", 1970 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    Biochemistry 9, 1224-1232.
    Correspondence includes referee's comments; photocopy of ms.
  - W.A. Gibbons, G. Nemethy, A. Stern and L.C. Craig "An approach to conformational analysis of peptides and proteins in solution based on a combination of nuclear magnetic resonance spectroscopy and conformational energy calculations", 1970 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    PNAS 67, 239-246.
  - H.C. Chen and L.C. Craig "A dialysis study on the conformation of lysozyme and its binding properties with N-acetyl-D-glucosamine", 1971 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Biorganic chemistry 1, 51-65.
    Correspondence; photocopies of ms (originally submitted to Biochemistry and includes referee's comments to Biochemistry); corrected galley proof; figures; photocopied material from Academic Press.
  - R.E. Galardy, M.P. Printz and L.C. Craig Tritium-hydrogen exchange of bacitracin A. Evidence for an intramolecular hydrogen bond", 1971 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Biochemistry 10, 2429-2436.
    Correspondence; photocopy of ms with corrections.
  - H.C. Chen, C.H. O'Neal and L.C. Craig "Rapid laboratory dialysis for aminoacylation assay of t-RNA", 1971 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Analytical chemistry 43, 1017-1020.
    Correspondence; photocopy of ms and photographs of some figures (some duplicates).
  - L.C. Craig "Separation of the parameters on which the physical fractionation of chemicals depends", 1972 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - M.P. Printz, H.P. Williams and L.C. Craig "Evidence for the presence of hydrogenbonded secondary structure in angiotensin II in aqueous solution", PNAS 69, 378-382, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Correspondence and photocopy of ms.
  - L.C. Craig and H.C. Chen "On a theory for the passive transport of solute through semipermeable membranes", 1972 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    PNAS 69, 702-705.
    Galley proof with corrections; typescript; background material.
  - R.C. Williams, D.A. Yphantis and L.C. Craig "Noncovalent association of tyrocidine B", 1972 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    Biochemistry 11, 70-77.
  - L.C. Craig, W.A. Gibbons and M. Prints "Studies of self-association of conformation of polypeptides", 1972 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    In: American Peptide Symposium, 2nd, Cleveland, 1970. Lane, Saul, ed. Progress in peptide research, II, New York, Gordon and Breach, pp. 217-233.
    Presented 1970 Cleveland 2nd American peptide symposium.
    Correspondence and typescript with corrections; some figures.
  - H-C Chen, L.C. Craig and E. Stoner "On the removal of residual carboxylic acid groups from cellulosic membranes and sephadex", 1972 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    Biochemistry 11, 3559-3564.
    Correspondence; referee's comments; galley proof with corrections.
  - L.C. Craig (#251 in Craig bibliography) "Methods for determining the conformation of peptides in solution", 1972 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    Presented 1971 Oct 1 as review [See Berson/Craig communication of Oct 29, 1970] (Reference cited below with #259 in Craig bibliography, pp. 447-454).
  - Craig, L.C, H. Kac, H.C Chen and M.P. Printz (#259) "Studies with synthetic ACTH analogs and other linear peptides", 1972 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    In: International Symposium on Protein and Polypeptide Hormones, 2nd, Liege, 1971.
    Structure-activity relationship of protein and polypeptide hormones; proceedings, Sept 28-0ct 1, 1970.
    Margoulies, M., and Greenwood, F.C eds. London, Excerpta Medica. pp. 176-180 (International Congress series, 241).
    Presented Oct 1 in session on "Conformation and receptors".
    Correspondence (some with H. Meinardi); programs (1 in French); Sept 28 Stop Press session program; photocopy and working ms (#259): also typescript (#251) with figures and photocopy of discussion; 3 mss by Fermandijian et al.
  - C.F. Beyer, L.C. Craig and W.A. Gibbons Interaction of the fluorescent probe 2-p-toluidinylnapthalene-6-sulfonate with peptides. Structural requirements for binding and fluorescence enhancement", 1972 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    Biochemistry 11, 4920-4926.
    Correspondence; photocopy of ms and corrected galley proof.
  - L.C. Craig, H.C. Chen and W.A. Gibbons "The use of thin film dialysis and high resolution NMR to study conformation and association phenomena", 1973 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    In: Erzin, M., ed., Polymer molecular weight methods. Washington, D.C, American Chemical Society, pp. 286-297. (Advances In chemistry series, 125).
    Presented 1971 ACS symposium on molecular weight determination.
    Correspondence includes referees comments; photocopies of ms includes working copies.
  - R.E. Galardy, R.S. Bockman, J.A. Sogn, W.A. Gibbons, M.P. Printz and L.C. Craig "Subtilopeptidase A cleavage in the cyclic region of the peptide antibiotic polymyxin B1", 1973 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    Int'l j peptide protein research 5, 455-461.
    Correspondence; photocopy of ms with figures; corrected galley proof.
  - H.E. Bleich, R.E. Galardy, M.P. Printz and L.C. Craig "Conformation studies of angiotensin peptides in aqueous solution by proton magnetic resonance", 1973 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    Biochemistry 12, 4950-4957.
    Correspondence includes referees comments; typescript of ms; corrected galley proof.
  - L.C. Craig, M.J. Harris, H. Bleich, H. Kac and P. Ziegler "On the conformation of linear peptides", 1973 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    Chimia 27, 381-382.
    Presented 1973 Apr 30 Bern, Switzerland, Berner Chemische Gesselschaft.
  - L.C. Craig "High resolution in counter-current extraction", 1973 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    J chromatography 83, 67-76.
    Correspondence and photocopies of ms, includes working copy.
    [Internal evidence indicates presented 1973 May 2-4 Interlaken, Symposium on column liquid chromatography].
  - L.C. Craig "Structural studies of naturally occurring cyclic polypeptides", 1973 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    In: Katsoyannis, P.G., ed., The chemistry of polypeptides. New York, Plenum Publishing Corp. pp. 155-168 (Book honoring L. Zervas).
  - M.J. Harris and L.C. Craig "A study of the parameters which determine the conformation of linear polypeptides in solution by synthesis of models and determination of thin film dialysis rates", 1974 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    Biochemistry 13.
    Correspondence Includes referees comments; photocopy of ms and corrected galley proof.
  - R.E. Galardy, L.C. Craig and M.P. Printz "Tritium-hydrogen exchange of the cyclic peptide polymyxin B1", 1974 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    Biochemistry 13, 1674-1677.
    Correspondence includes referees comments; photocopy of revised ms and typescript and photocopy of original ms; galley proof with corrections; figures and working material.
  - J.A. Sogn, L.C. Craig and W.A. Gibbons "The complete assignment of the 13C nuclear magnetic resonance spectrum of the decapeptide gramicidin S-A by selective biosynthetic enrichment studies", 1974 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    JACS 96, 3306-3309.
  - R.E. Galardy, L.C. Craig, J.D. Jamieson and M. Printz "Photoaffinity labeling of peptide hormone binding sites", 1974 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    J biol chem 249, 3510-3518.
  - C. Beyer, W.A. Gibbons and L.C. Craig "Heterogeneous tryptophan environments in the cyclic peptides tyrocidines B and C", 1974 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    J biol chem 249, 3204-3211.
    Correspondence; typescript of ms.
  - J.A. Sogn, L.C. Craig and W.A. Gibbons "13c-13c coupling constants in a series of 13c - enriched amino acids", 1974 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    JACS 96, 4694-4696.
    Correspondence; photocopies of ms and working material.
  - J.A. Sogn, L.C. Craig and W.A. Gibbons "Separation of amino acid mixtures enriched in stable isotopes", 1974 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    Int'l j peptide protein research 6, 353-356.
  - L.C. Craig, D. Cowburn and H. Bleich "Methods for the study of the conformation of small peptide hormones and antibiotics in solution", 1975 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    Annual review biochemistry 44, 477-490.
    Correspondence includes list of topics and authors of Annual review of biochemistry 43 (1974).
  - C.F. Beyer, L.C. Craig, W.A. Gibbons and J.W. Longworth "Studies of the conformation and self-association of cyclic decapeptides triplet-triplet energy transfer", 1976 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    In: Birks, J.B., ed., Excited states of biological molecules; based on the proceedings of the Int'l Conf. at the Calhouste Gul-benkian Foundation Centre, Lisbon, Portugal on April 18-24, 1974. New York, John Wiley & Sons. pp. 411-424.
    Photocopy of ms.
  - [NPI] L.C. Craig, D. Cowburn, G. Schaetlin, J.H. Cort and R. Walter "On the effect of certain cations on the conformation in solution of angiotensin II" (Box 30, Folder 15)
    [Originally submitted in 1973 and resubmitted in 1974 to Molecular Pharmacology but does not appear to have been published].
    Correspondence includes referees comments; photocopies of revised and original ms; working material with laboratory data; figures.
  - Publications not listed in Craig bibliography: Mss
    - L.C. Craig (Book review) Raven, H.M. and Stamm, W. Gegenstrom-Verteilung, Julius Springer, Berlin W. 1953. vii + 81 pp, 1954 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      JACS 76, 4055-4056.
      Correspondence includes some with H.M. Raven in German; typescript and photocopy of review.
    - L.C. Craig and D. Craig "Laboratory extraction and countercurrent distribution", 1956; 4 folders
      In: Weissberger, A. ed., Technique of organic chemistry. Part I. Separation and purification, New York, Interscience Publishers, v. 3, pp. 149-332.
      - Correspondence; galley proofs with corrections (apparently from original publication) - note page numbers sic (Chapter II, Section I to VII) (Box 31, Folder 2-3)
      - Photographic prints of figures #1-96; lacking 22 (Box 31, Folder 4)
        Includes some duplicates and photocopies.
      - Chapter II, Section IX by E.G. Scheibel, Galley proof with corrections and figures; figure 123 lacking, pp. 332-393 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - L.C. Craig, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 6)
      "Impurities".
      In: Clark, G.L., ed., The encyclopedia of chemistry. New York, Rheinhold Publishing Co. pp. 487-488.
      Correspondence; typescript and photocopy of ms.
    - L.C. Craig, 1957 (Box 31, Folder 7)
      "Extraction".
      In: Yoe, J.H. and Koch, H.J. Trace analysis; papers presented at a symposium on trace analysis held at The New York Academy of Medicine, New York, N.Y., Nov. 2,3,4, 1955. New York, John Wiley, pp. 102-125.
      Correspondence; typed record of questions and comments and photocopy of ms.
    - L.C. Craig. (Book reviews) Zechmeister, L., ed., Progress in the chemistry of organic natural products, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 8)
      v. 15 and 16, Vienna, Springer, 1958.
      [v. 15] Science 130, 498-499.
      [v. 16] Science 130, 704.
      Correspondence and photocopies of published reviews.
    - L.C. Craig. (Book review) Harris, R.S., Marrian, G.F. and Thimann, K.V. eds., Vitamins and hormones, 1959 (Box 32, Folder 1)
      Advances in research and applications v. XVI, New York, Academic Press, 1958.
      JACS 81, 4759-4760.
      Correspondence and typescripts of review.
    - L.C. Craig. (Book review) Morris, C.J.O.R. and Morris, P., Separation methods in biochemistry. New York, interscience, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 2)
      Science 146,1571-1572.
      Correspondence and photocopy of published review.
    - L.C. Craig "Dialysis", 1966 (Box 32, Folder 2)
      In: Encyclopedia of polymer science and technology. New York, Interscience Publishers v. 4. pp. 824-857.
      Correspondence and working copy of ms.
    - L.C. Craig. (Book review) Pratt, H.R.C. Countercurrent separation processes, Amsterdam, Elsevier Publishing Co., 1967, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 4)
      Analytical chemistry 40, 93A (No. 1).
      Correspondence and photocopy of review.
    - L.C. Craig "Biographical note. Walter A. Jacobs 1883-1967" (Box 32, Folder 5)
      RU review (1967 Nov.-Dec.) 23-25.
      Photocopy of published ms and working copy.
      [See also under: Jacobs, W.A. in box no. 6].
    - L.C. Craig "Walter A. Jacobs obituary" (for American Society for Pharmacology and Experimental Therapeutics - written 1967 Aug 2), 1968 (Box 32, Folder 6)
      The Pharmacologist (1968 March) pp (?).
      Copy of ms.
    - A. Stern, W.A. Gibbons and L.C. Craig "Studies on the tertiary and quaternary structure of cyclic antibiotic polypeptides", 1971 (Box 32, Folder 7)
      In: Franconi, C, ed., Magnetic resonances in biological research. New York, Gordon and Breach, pp. 327-335.
      Correspondence; list of conference participants; photocopy of presentation and published ms.
      Presented 1969 Sept 14-17 University of Cagliari, Italy, Int'l conference on magnetic resonances in biological research.
    - W.A. Gibbons, J, Sogn, A. Stern and L.C. Craig and L.F. Johnson. "Natural abundance carbon-13 NMR studies of amino acids and complex peptides", 1970 (Box 32, Folder 8)
      Federation proceedings 29, 464 abs.
      Photocopy of published abstract.
      Presented at 1970 Apr 12-17 Atlantic City, NJ, 54th Annual FASEB meeting.
    - H.C. Chen and L.C. Craig "Removal of residual fixed charges on cellulosic membranes and sephadex", 1972 (Box 32, Folder 9)
      Federation proceedings 31, 496 abs.
      Photocopy of published abstract Indications are presented by H.C. Chen 1972 Apr 9-14 Atlantic City, NJ 56th Annual FASEB meeting.
      [See under Chen, H.C. for typescript of presentation in box no. 4].
    - L.C. Craig and J. Sogn "Isolation of antibiotics by countercurrent distribution", 1975 (Box 32, Folder 10)
      In: Hash, J.H., ed., Methods in enzymology v. 43: Antibiotics, New York, Academic Press, pp. 320-346.